https://love-of-roses.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Search for:
Search
Menu HomeTypesAntique RosesDamask RosesClimbing RosesEnglish RosesFloribunda RosesGrandifloraHybrid Tea RosesMiniature RosesPolyantha RosesRambling RosesWild RosesStyles & MoreOur Top Five ListsThornless RosesStandard RosesColorsBlack RosesBlue Roses?Multi Colored RosesOrange RosesPeach And ApricotPink RosesShades Of PurpleRed RosesWhite RosesYellow RosesCareGetting Started With RosesDeal With PestsRose DiseasesTIPS ABOUT…Arches, Arbors, TrellisHow To Prune RosesCare For Cut RosesDeadheadingPlanting/TransplantRose LeavesWinterizing RosesPROPOGATIONAll About PropogatingNotable Rose BreedersArt & GardensGardens & FestivalsTrevor Griffiths Rose GardenAustralian Inland Botanic GardensMissouri Botanical GardenChicago Flower ShowPortland Rose GardenInternational Rose Test GardenMy Rose GardenARTArt/ImagesRose ClipartRose Image GalleriesRoses WallpaperRose PaintingsDrawings Of RosesLITERATURERoses In HistoryMeaning Of RosesRose QuotesRose PoetryAll NaturalORGANICOrganic Tips/ArticlesTINCTURES/RECIPESNatural Rose RemediesRose HipsHip And Petal RecipesHow To Make TinctureSCENT/CRAFTS ETCMaking PotpourriFragrance And ScentHow To Press RosesFind A RoseSearchHome » Privacy PolicyWe are committed to protecting your privacyWe recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use love-of-roses.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.love-of-roses.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers’, consumers’ and online visitors’ privacy on our website.Personal InformationLove-of-roses.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, and used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.Once information is reviewed, we discard it or store it in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties.Use of Cookies and Web BeaconsWe use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser to enable our system to recognize your browser.The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have come to the site for the first time, or have returned to a specific page. If you personalize the site’s pages, or register with any of our site’s services, a cookie enables rosesgalore.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying settings in your browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. Beacons are also referred to as web bugs. They are commonly used by sites that use third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a website. As you browse this website, Google Analytics and advertising cookies will be placed on your computer to collect demographic and interest information, but we do not tie the cookie to any personal information that you provide to us. If you do not wish your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you may use their opt-out tool… https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These companies use cookies and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many times you’ve seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information from our website. Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads. This cookie enables Google to serve ads to users based on their visits to other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions should not cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.Children’s Online Privacy Protection ActThis website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.Non-Personal InformationIn some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.Release of InformationIf  love-of-roses.com is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.How You Can Correct or Remove InformationWe provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records, or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us page.Updates and Effective Daterosesgalore.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.Agreeing to TermsIf you do not agree to lov-of-roses.com privacy policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy. CategoriesCategoriesSelect CategoryAntiquebi-colorClimbing RosesColor-BlendEnglish RosesFloribundaGrandifloraHybrid TeaOrange RosesOther Garden PlantsOur GardenPeach/Apricot RosesPink RosesRambling RosesRed RosesShades Of PurpleShrubStriped RosesUncategorizedWhite RosesWild RosesYellow Roses
Archives Archives Select Month November 2019 October 2019 September 2019
TagsBlooms-In-Flushes Burgundy Disease-Prone Disease-Resistant Double Easy-Care Handpaint-Style Highly-Fragrant Kordes Light-Frangrance Low-Fragrance Med-Fragrance No-Fragrance Perpetual-Blooming Repeat-Blooming Semi-Double Single Single-Blooming Very-Thorny
ContactPrivacy PolicyAbout UsRecent Posts Lorraine Lee John Cabot Rose Multiflora Rose Rosa Canina Copyright© 2007-2019 Love-Of-Roses.com. All Rights Reserved.
Scroll back to top This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
